Y'all, we are here recording these episodes of Small Doses Podcast.
And I mean, I'm just so proud of the way that we have continued to keep these conversations going up, up, up, up, up.
And that is going to continue with this next episode.
We have got Kadida Stone, who is a part of this landmark case that is changing the redistricting in Alabama
so that we can get more black folks votes to count.
Now, we all know Alabama has a history of voter suppression, of gerrymandering, of just being straight up racist.
And so we got to talk about it.
We are about to be into an election year and we need to make sure that folks are getting just as much right to vote as they deserve.
And so we have got this sister here to talk us through side effects of voting rights in Alabama.
So I would love to hear from you all because we're not just going to talk about as it relates to Alabama,
but of voting in general, why it matters, what does redistricting do, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
Drop your questions in the comments.
I know we've got a lot of politically inclined folks here and I want to hear from you.
So get right here.
Small Doses side effects of voting rights in Alabama with Kadida Stone.